<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jacob Chvatal</title>
    <link>https://confident-mclean-736f9a.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jacob Chvatal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 11:12:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://confident-mclean-736f9a.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building this Website</title>
      <link>https://confident-mclean-736f9a.netlify.com/projects/building-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 11:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://confident-mclean-736f9a.netlify.com/projects/building-site/</guid>
      <description>This website is written with org-mode, powered by Hugo, and hosted with Netlify.
Why?
I had several needs for making this website.
 Easily updatable. My last website was my first serious attempt at web development without using a framework - making use only of HTML, CSS and Javascript - and hosted on an archaic static site deployment platform. As impressive as the Three.js visualizations on the site were, I had to dive into the code, then drag-and-drop upload the individual files to a host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CDK Global Internship</title>
      <link>https://confident-mclean-736f9a.netlify.com/projects/cdk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://confident-mclean-736f9a.netlify.com/projects/cdk/</guid>
      <description>At CDK Global, I leveraged React.js and Redux to, along with a high school intern and two college interns, develop software used by an internal credit reporting team to monitor the number of credit checks made by individual car dealerships.
Tech Stack We built a full-stack web application with a React.js front-end, making use of both Material UI and CDK Global&#39;s proprietary React components as well as Redux and thunk for asynchronous global state management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Style</title>
      <link>https://confident-mclean-736f9a.netlify.com/thoughts/style/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://confident-mclean-736f9a.netlify.com/thoughts/style/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m passionate about many things, one of which being my style.
Let&#39;s define style as something cohesive - this style is composed of every aspect of one&#39;s life, from how they present themselves with their clothing to their organizational systems and their attitude towards their work.
The curation of a set of strong, cohesive principles are able to strengthen the ability of an individual to exude greater confidence, enhance productivity, and improve livelihood.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>